

 \sim

malusarea111@gmail.com

8855940530

in

linkedin.com/in/aniket-s-malusare

github.com/malusarea06

SKILLS

Python 3.0

Flask

Core Java

MySQL

Firebase

GIT

JIRA

Selenium

REST API

Agile Practioner

PostgreSQL

DBeaver

BitBucket

Appium

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Trekking

Gymnasium

Listening Music

Aniket Malusare

Python Developer

Aniket Malusare has over 2 years of experience in Automation/Backend Development with proficiency in Python 3.0, designing REST API using Flask, Selenium, MySQL, Firebase and familiar with Jenkins. Working experience in Agile/Scrum workflow. ISTQB Certified.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Python DeveloperDigit Insurance pvt Ltd.

10/2019 - Present

Working with BOT team to develop bots for Operations team, Claims Team to automate the process.

Python,Flask,Selenium,PostgreSQL

- Involved in understanding business requirements, design and implementation using python.
- Developed bots using selenium web driver, service based bots and also developed Rest API using flask framework for OPS team.
- Used Pandas library to perform operations on Excel File.
- □ Worked on Microsoft Graph API,O365 library to access outlook calendars and events.
- Used PostgreSQL, DBeaver to create database and perform CRUD operations.
- Used GIT bash to push,commit code on BitBucket

YOMA (Myanmar Bank) Capco Technolgies pvt Ltd.

09/2017 - 04/2019 Yoma DB Basics

This is a Hybrib Mobile Application For Mobile Banking on android and ios. This application is used all yoma bank customers for financial operations.

Python,Flask,MySQL

- Involved in the understanding of business requirement, analysis, design, implementation and coding in python using Flask.
- Developed REST API's using Flask.
- Developing application to perform various different operations like send money, create FD, smart account, notification management, viewing transaction history.
- Conceptualized, Designed and Developed module for banking customers.
- Implemented Push Notification for Android using GCM, Microsoft Azure
- Wrote clean, clear, efficient, well tested, and maintainable code.

SCB iPlan - Leading Bank of Thailand Capco Technologies Pvt Ltd

01/2018 - 03/2018

Automation Test Engineer

This project involves an iPad application which was used by the Insurance agents of one of Asia's leading commercial bank to sell various insurance products of the Bank.

Selenium, Appium, Cucumber

- Identified test scenarios, estimate test effort and supported test leads in test planning
- Maintained regression test suite and other testing scenario
- Involved in Agile testing methodology
- Participated and contributed in daily Scrum meetings.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Engineering (Computer) Pune University

06/2014 - 06/2017

Courses

Computer Engineering

63%